[
  { "question": "0 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 1", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 2", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 3", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 4", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 5", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 6", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 7", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 8", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "0 x 9", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "1 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "1 x 1", "answer": 1 },
  { "question": "1 x 2", "answer": 2 },
  { "question": "1 x 3", "answer": 3 },
  { "question": "1 x 4", "answer": 4 },
  { "question": "1 x 5", "answer": 5 },
  { "question": "1 x 6", "answer": 6 },
  { "question": "1 x 7", "answer": 7 },
  { "question": "1 x 8", "answer": 8 },
  { "question": "1 x 9", "answer": 9 },
  { "question": "2 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "2 x 1", "answer": 2 },
  { "question": "2 x 2", "answer": 4 },
  { "question": "2 x 3", "answer": 6 },
  { "question": "2 x 4", "answer": 8 },
  { "question": "2 x 5", "answer": 10 },
  { "question": "2 x 6", "answer": 12 },
  { "question": "2 x 7", "answer": 14 },
  { "question": "2 x 8", "answer": 16 },
  { "question": "2 x 9", "answer": 18 },
  { "question": "3 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "3 x 1", "answer": 3 },
  { "question": "3 x 2", "answer": 6 },
  { "question": "3 x 3", "answer": 9 },
  { "question": "3 x 4", "answer": 12 },
  { "question": "3 x 5", "answer": 15 },
  { "question": "3 x 6", "answer": 18 },
  { "question": "3 x 7", "answer": 21 },
  { "question": "3 x 8", "answer": 24 },
  { "question": "3 x 9", "answer": 27 },
  { "question": "4 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "4 x 1", "answer": 4 },
  { "question": "4 x 2", "answer": 8 },
  { "question": "4 x 3", "answer": 12 },
  { "question": "4 x 4", "answer": 16 },
  { "question": "4 x 5", "answer": 20 },
  { "question": "4 x 6", "answer": 24 },
  { "question": "4 x 7", "answer": 28 },
  { "question": "4 x 8", "answer": 32 },
  { "question": "4 x 9", "answer": 36 },
  { "question": "5 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "5 x 1", "answer": 5 },
  { "question": "5 x 2", "answer": 10 },
  { "question": "5 x 3", "answer": 15 },
  { "question": "5 x 4", "answer": 20 },
  { "question": "5 x 5", "answer": 25 },
  { "question": "5 x 6", "answer": 30 },
  { "question": "5 x 7", "answer": 35 },
  { "question": "5 x 8", "answer": 40 },
  { "question": "5 x 9", "answer": 45 },
  { "question": "6 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "6 x 1", "answer": 6 },
  { "question": "6 x 2", "answer": 12 },
  { "question": "6 x 3", "answer": 18 },
  { "question": "6 x 4", "answer": 24 },
  { "question": "6 x 5", "answer": 30 },
  { "question": "6 x 6", "answer": 36 },
  { "question": "6 x 7", "answer": 42 },
  { "question": "6 x 8", "answer": 48 },
  { "question": "6 x 9", "answer": 54 },
  { "question": "7 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "7 x 1", "answer": 7 },
  { "question": "7 x 2", "answer": 14 },
  { "question": "7 x 3", "answer": 21 },
  { "question": "7 x 4", "answer": 28 },
  { "question": "7 x 5", "answer": 35 },
  { "question": "7 x 6", "answer": 42 },
  { "question": "7 x 7", "answer": 49 },
  { "question": "7 x 8", "answer": 56 },
  { "question": "7 x 9", "answer": 63 },
  { "question": "8 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "8 x 1", "answer": 8 },
  { "question": "8 x 2", "answer": 16 },
  { "question": "8 x 3", "answer": 24 },
  { "question": "8 x 4", "answer": 32 },
  { "question": "8 x 5", "answer": 40 },
  { "question": "8 x 6", "answer": 48 },
  { "question": "8 x 7", "answer": 56 },
  { "question": "8 x 8", "answer": 64 },
  { "question": "8 x 9", "answer": 72 },
  { "question": "9 x 0", "answer": 0 },
  { "question": "9 x 1", "answer": 9 },
  { "question": "9 x 2", "answer": 18 },
  { "question": "9 x 3", "answer": 27 },
  { "question": "9 x 4", "answer": 36 },
  { "question": "9 x 5", "answer": 45 },
  { "question": "9 x 6", "answer": 54 },
  { "question": "9 x 7", "answer": 63 },
  { "question": "9 x 8", "answer": 72 },
  { "question": "9 x 9", "answer": 81 }
]

